Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- California CIO Council, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: CIO Community Services Handbook, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: California CIO Industrial Union Council
  - Item 2: Hand book for Union Counselors, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Report of The Community Services Committee, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Ray P. Haeckel
- California CIO Council, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Council Newsletter, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.5:no.3 (1955:Feb. 18)
- California CIO Council, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of First Constitutional Convention of California CIO Council on Political Education, 1958; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report of Officers to the 1st Constitutional convention, 1958, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The moral case against right-to-work laws, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: They're trying to cut your paycheck, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: California CIO Council's 10 point program to halt growing unemployment., 1954; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Constitution, rules and order of business, California Labor Council on Political Education, adopted by the California Labor COPE Convention, San Francisco, December 9, 1958, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Author: California Labor Council on Political Education.
  - Item 7: Policy statement on attempts to destroy American free trade unionism in California, adopted by the General Board of California CIO Council on Political Education (California CIO COPE), September 12, 1957, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Whole community suffers from mis-named "Right-to-work" laws, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Council newsletter, 1952; Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.12 (1952:Mar 10)
  - Item 2: Factual Ammunition, 1950-1951 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.1,4,-5,8-11
  - Item 3: Factual Ammunition, 1952; Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-4
  - Item 4: Report on 1954 general election results in California, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Resolution No. 14-55; Submitted by: Executive Board, Colorado CIO Council - Union Labels, 1956; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Resolution, Submitted by: Executive Board, Colorado CIO Council - Right-to scab legislation, 1954; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Resolution, Submitted by: Local Union No. 8412, CWA - State - CIO Community Services Committee, 1954; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Connecticut CIO News, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.10-11 (1940-1941)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Legislative report to the 18th Annual Convention of the Connecticut State Industrial Union Council...(AFL-CIO), January 20-21-22, 1956, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Author: Connecticut State Industrial Union Council
  - Item 2: Practical guide to workmen's compensation: in question and answer form for Union Officers, Stewards and Members, 1952; Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: By-laws, District of Columbia Industrial Union Council-CIO, 1949; Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Minutes [of the] Executive Board, DC CIO Council, July 24, 1950, Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Georgia Council Spotlight - v.6, 7-8 (1957), Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: CIO-Editors Assoc. of Illinois, Special Issue, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Officers' report, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.12-20 (1954)
  - Item 2: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-9,12-15,17-23 (1955)
  - Item 3: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.7:no.8-9 (1958)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-9,11-24 (1957)
  - Item 2: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.7,no.1-7 (1958)
  - Item 3: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.4:no.24-26 (1955)
  - Item 4: CIO Fact Sheet, [Indiana State CIO Council], 1956; Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-20,23-25 (1956)
- Indiana State Industrial Union Council, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Indiana Stateand rules and regulations governing Indiana CIO-PAC, 1952; Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Author: Indiana State Industrial Union Council
  - Item 2: Political Action Manual, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Author: Indiana State CIO-PAC
- Indiana State Industrial Union Council, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Indiana 'Right-to-work' Law, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Unemployment Compensation, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Author: Indiana State AFL-CIO
  - Item 3: Resolutions and Committee reports: passed by the 10th Annual Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor-management round-table; conference program, 1949; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: What every worker should know about the Massachusetts Workmen's Compensation Law, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Author: Bertram A. Petkun
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution of Conn. State Industrial Union Council, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: $100 retired pay is urged by Tobin, 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Boston asks new law to gain 'labor peace', 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: CIO Council, Catholic labor group break, 1953-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: CIO may force tax vote, 1953-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: CIO to purge Reds in Massachusetts, 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Conn. House, 164 to 97, rejects CIO Counsel as Judge, 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Conn. Vote backs CIO aid, 1953-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: jobless pay liberalization opposed, 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Text of address by Truman at Detroit labor rally, 1953-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Williams-CIO slate wins by acclamation, 1953-1955 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Michigan CIO Council, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 10th Annual Leadership Institute, FDR-CIO Labor Center, Michigan CIO Council, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Notes: Local manual
  - Item 2: Steward's guide, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Author: Michigan CIO Council
  - Item 3: The CIO Radio Activator, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.IV
  - Item 4: Michigan CIO Leadership, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Now What?, Helpful hints for Stewards, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Author: Michigan CIO Council Education Dept.
  - Item 6: Planning a local union education program, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Plant Committee and Stewards' Manual, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Promotion manual an aid to CIO locals to promote their various programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Public relations promotion publicity, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Publicity manual, to aid CIO locals to gain good publicity, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The mimeo handbook, 1947; Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Michigan CIO Council, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Collect your unemployment Insurance, 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A message from the CIO - Tractors for you - Ham and Eggs for us, 1950; Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Don't blow your top, organize a Co-Op, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Publicity manual, to aid CIO locals to gain good publicity, 1950; Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Steward's and Committeeman's Pocket Guide, 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The Michigan CIO Council and the Kent County CIO Council present2nd annual city-county government institute, Mar. 9-11, 1953, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: What is the Michigan CIO Council Social Security plan?, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Yes sir, prosperity for some!, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Anti-Red stand voted in NJ CIO session, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Asks ban on bowling unit, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Cashmore stand splits state CIO, 1951-1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Chance to register on job given workers in 3 big Jersey plants, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: CIO convention gives Hennings its endorsement, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: CIO Council lays victory to young folk and women, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: CIO opposes choice, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: CIO opposes Jersey bonus, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Communist issue up in Jersey CIO, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Dual roles charged to Jersey officials, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Holderman gets Jersey labor Joe, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Jersey bills denounced, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Jersey CIO advises Wene to drop race, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Jersey CIO asks 'essential' laws, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Jersey CIO boss pledges fight on gasoline price-fixing bills, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Jersey CIO leader assailed on politics, 1951-1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Jersey CIO proposes corporate tax rise, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Jersey CIO proposes corporate tax rise, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Jersey CIO reports joblessness serious, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Jersey CIO urges action on idleness, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Jersey promises CIO to speed jobless pay, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Jersey's CIO votes 3d term for Roosevelt, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Lack of labor unions in Asia benefits Reds, Army Secretary tells Jersey CIO session, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: New Haven CIO man named school aide, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: New tack is urged in labor relations, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Protest parkway tolls, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: State CIO assails Eisenhower regime, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: State CIO backs Roosevelt alone, 1951-1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: State CIO decries police union ban, 1951-1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Unity advanced by Jersey CIO, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Vote at 18 favored by Jersey CIO unit, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Jersey CIO forms own inquiry body, 1949-1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Jersey CIO looks to state merger, 1946-1955 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: O'Dwyer tells CIO Congress 'stalls' on Truman policy, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Roosevelt tells CIO he's in race to stay, 1951-1954 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: State CIO hints cashmore backing, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Wene fails to get Jersey CIO backing, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Workers in Jersey to register on job, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
- New Jersey State Industrial Union Council, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: CIO calls for probe of Unemployment Compensation Commission, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: New Jersey State Industrial Union Council
- New Jersey State Industrial Union Council., Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A comprehensive tax program for New Jersey, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: New Jersey State Industrial Union Council.
  - Item 2: Analysis of the 1952 elections in New Jersey., Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: By convention action, 1951; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: By convention action: New Jersey CIO policies for 1954-1955: Text of the major resolutions and reports adopted by the delegates to the 13th regular constitutional convention of the New Jersey State CIO in Atlantic City, December 4-6, 1953, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: New Jersey State Congress of Industrial Organizations
  - Item 5: Report of the executive officers to the special PAC-legislative conference of the New Jersey State CIO Industrial Union Council, January 15, 1949, Trenton, N.J., Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The effectiveness of CIO-PAC in New Jersey in 1950; officers report. A complete study on the methods, problems and results obtained in New Jersey during the 1950 congressional elections by the CIO Political Action Committee, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The New Jersey workmen's compensation law: what every worker should know about it, 1951; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
- New Jersey State Industrial Union Council., Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: For adults only, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Author: New Jersey State CIO- PAC
  - Item 2: A comprehensive tax program for New Jersey, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: CIO manual on unemployment State Laws, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Notes: Local manual. Labeled: "reference copy do not take"
  - Item 4: Economic controls in our national emergency; summary of a conference ..., 1951; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Author: Rutgers University. Institute of Management and Labor Relations
- New York State CIO, Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: New York State CIO Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Author: New York State CIO
    Notes: vol.1:no.3 (1952)
  - Item 2: New York State CIO Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-3 (1953)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Don't let them undermine worker security and community welfare, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Published specifically for New York State CIO Council
  - Item 2: Don't wait another 20 years, 1959; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Higher education and labor, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Author: Louis Hollander
    Notes: Reprinted from Higher Education and the Society it serves
  - Item 4: Labor's challenge, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Remarks made by Louis Hollander
  - Item 5: Promises and performance, 1954; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Special Bulletin
  - Item 6: The BIG change in Washington, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: The Community and Higher Education, 1958; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The growth in management science and its impact on management-worker relations, 1958; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Twenty years of New Deal and Fair Deal achievement, 1954; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Written expecially for the New York State CIO Council
  - Item 10: You pay the bill, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Notes: Local 'Special Bulletin'
  - Item 11: CIO and the community in New York State, 1951-1952, a report (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations. (U.S.) Industrial Union Councils. New York (State)
  - Item 12: CIO and the community. President's report to the New York State CIO, January, 1951., Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). New York (State). Industrial Union Council.
  - Item 13: Letter from Louis Hollander to All Affiliates of the New York State CIO Council, 1949; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Press release, Aug. 23, 1956 - NYS DOL, "Address of Isador Lubin", Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Resolutions submitted to the Ninth Annual Convention of the New York State CIO, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Times, Friday, Sept. 7, 1951, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Fair deal drive, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Alcoa contract opposed by CIO, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Anti-crime drive in Jersey mapped, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Bill would revise teacher licensing, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Board challenges Hollander, Moss, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Cashmore backed by the state CIO, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Cashmore praises state labor units, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: CIO asks Albany aid fight on curbs, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: CIO asks Desapio to reject Donovan, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: CIO asks tight welfare-fund lid, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: CIO bars 'Hack' for Governor; wants a new deal, fair deal man, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: CIO bids Wagner seek Senate seat, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: CIO cleans house, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: CIO favors veto of grievance bill, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: CIO in state to open 4-way drive at Albany, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: CIO leader asks state health plan, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: CIO leaders plan fight on leftists, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: CIO not yet backing anyone as Governor, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: CIO offers plan for union funds, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: CIO offers plan for union funds, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: CIO official weighs 'defiance' of court, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: CIO state board Parley due Jan. 14, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: CIO unions fear cuts in job funds, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: CIO unions to map new council here, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: CIO urges state to control rents, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: CIO will organize new council here, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: CIO won't accept COD candidates, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: CIO-Council reborn as anti-red group, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: City CIO Council ended life 'broke', 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Congress 'stalls' O'Dwyer tells CIO, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Court fight by CIO for sick aid Looms, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Democrats plot deal, Curran says, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Dewey CIO clash on idle-pay plans, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Employment held markedly better, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Fight pay-freeze state, CIO urged, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Hearn's threatened with mass picketing, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Hollander expects victory for Pecora, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Hollander traces labor's evolution, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Honor Danish unionist, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Intimidation effort seen in Hearn Strike, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Lehman sees peril in rivals' victory, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Lehman to speak before state CIO, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Lehman, CIO group back Roosevelt Jr., 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Lynch is endorsed by the state CIO, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: Many rules about jobless called rigid, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: New fund sought for compensation, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: Opinions divided on disability bill, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: PAC to support Truman man only, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Party 'gang-up' on labor charged, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Pay board scored by one of members, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Pecora candidacy endorsed by CIO rival asked to quit, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Pecora promises a 'labor cabinet', 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: Quill police plot seen by Riegelman, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 55: Quill re-elected by city CIO unit, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 56: Requisites of CIO set for Governor, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 57: Riegelman scores Quill as a bully, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Seek Albany aid in fight on union curbs, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 59: State aid sought for $100 pensions, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 60: State CIO accepts Dewey challenge, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 61: State CIO adopts curb on 'marches', 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 62: State CIO asks $1.25 wage floor, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 63: State CIO bars Mayor as speaker, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 64: State CIO chiefs to back Cashmore, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 65: State CIO delegates Start drive to draft Wagner for Senate bid, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 66: State CIO fights rent rise proposal, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 67: State CIO for Harriman maps a $50,000 TV drive, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 68: State CIO group to expel Potash, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 69: State CIO maps TV-Radio program, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 70: State CIO moves to draft Wagner, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 71: State CIO rebuffs left, backs ER 4-1, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 72: State CIO seeks curb on insurance, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 73: State CIO slated to assail Soviet, 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 74: State CIO to direct strike at Hearns with Committee from 5unions in charge, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 75: State CIO to fight injury law shift, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 76: State CIO to map drive, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 77: State CIO to open drive for Lehman, 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 78: State CIO urges full term for Lehman; demands direct election of educators, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 79: State CIO urges lawmakers meet, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 80: State CIO votes ban on Communists, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 81: State labor joins to elect Lehman, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 82: Text of Wagners address to the state CIO convention, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 83: Truman hat to land on union Chief's head, propelled by Wager and Presidential Size, 1949-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)